l should have sent you to the custom
car cover place in AItadena.
(Howard:)They have her pattern on file.
Ha-ha. Humorous.
(Sheldon:)Now, will you please present
my paper to Professor Hawking?
- l don't know.
- Oh, for heaven's sake.
l did your laundry.
l pee-pee-proofed your beIt buckles.
l even sprained my wrist
helping your mother lift her bosom.
(Howard:)All right, Sheldon. There's only
one thing left I want you to do.
(Howard:)- Don't worry, it's an easy one.
- Okay.
(Howard:)Give me a compliment.
(Penny:)Fine.
(Sheldon:)You have very tiny hands.
(Howard:)No. About my job.
l want you to tell me
I'm good at what I do.
(Sheldon:)You're obviously good
at what you do.
(Howard:)Well, then, why are you always ripping
on me?
(Sheldon:)Oh, I understand the confusion.